export const data = [
    {
      question: "Which agent has the ultimate ability 'Viper's Pit'?",
      option1: "Viper",
      option2: "Omen",
      option3: "Phoenix",
      option4: "Sage",
      ans: 1, 
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of Phoenix's ultimate ability?",
      option1: "Run It Back",
      option2: "Hot Hands",
      option3: "Blaze",
      option4: "Radiant Flame",
      ans: 1, 
    },
    {
      question: "Which agent's ultimate ability is 'Resurrection'?",
      option1: "Sage",
      option2: "Jett",
      option3: "Breach",
      option4: "Reyna",
      ans: 1, 
    },
    {
      question: "Which agent has the ultimate ability 'X-Ray Vision'?",
      option1: "Sova",
      option2: "Brimstone",
      option3: "Omen",
      option4: "Killjoy",
      ans: 3, 
    },
    {
      question: "What does the ultimate ability 'Run It Back' do?",
      option1: "Allows Phoenix to teleport to his original position after death",
      option2: "Summons a wall of fire",
      option3: "Heals Phoenix instantly",
      option4: "Increases Phoenix's movement speed",
      ans: 1, 
    },
    {
      question: "Which agent's ultimate is called 'Hunter's Fury'?",
      option1: "Cypher",
      option2: "Omen",
      option3: "Sova",
      option4: "Raze",
      ans: 3, 
    },
    {
      question: "What is Killjoy's ultimate ability called?",
      option1: "Lockdown",
      option2: "Lockdown X",
      option3: "Nanoswarm",
      option4: "Lockdown Zone",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which agent's ultimate is 'Vigilant'?",
      option1: "Breach",
      option2: "Brimstone",
      option3: "Raze",
      option4: "Omen",
      ans: 4, 
    },
    {
      question: "Which agent uses the ultimate ability 'Nightfall'?",
      option1: "Jett",
      option2: "Sova",
      option3: "Skye",
      option4: "KAY/O",
      ans: 4, 
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of Sageâ€™s ultimate ability?",
      option1: "Resurrection",
      option2: "Healing Orb",
      option3: "Barrier Orb",
      option4: "Resurrect",
      ans: 1, 
    },
  ];
  